Guide to the Mary Kennedy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- December 1988 Acquisition, 60; (69 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Kennedy, Mary, correspondence with Robert Niles Jr. (Box 54)
  - Kennedy, Patrick, correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 54)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, correspondence with Foster Kennedy (Box 54)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, correspondence with Foster and James Kennedy (Box 54)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, correspondence with James Kennedy (Box 54)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, correspondence with Mary Kennedy, 8 (Box 54)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, papers (Box 54)
  - Drawings by others (Box 55)
  - Business and financial papers (Box 55)
  - Comments by others regarding "The Bourrichon" (Box 55)
  - Comments made on poems by others (Box 55)
  - Correspondence with various publishers (Box 55)
  - Credit cards and membership cards (Box 55)
  - Documents regarding "Emily and the Green Circle" (Box 55)
  - Documents regarding health, including obituaries (Box 55)
  - Documents regarding property (Box 55)
  - Drafts of business correspondence (Box 55)
  - Drawings (Box 55)
  - Estate and medical records (Box 55)
  - Make-up chart (Box 55)
  - Medical records and bills (Box 55)
  - Memorabilia (Box 55)
  - Notes from others regarding her poems (Box 55)
  - Photographs (Box 55)
  - Printed poems (Box 55)
  - Professional correspondence, 2 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 10 (Box 56)
  - Greeting cards, 2 (Box 56)
  - Greeting cards (Box 57)
  - Invitations (Box 57)
  - Playbill (Box 57)
  - Professional correspondence, 3 (Box 57)
  - Christmas cards, 7 (Box 58)
  - Alexander, Betty, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Benet, Laura (Box 59)
  - Boissevain, Robert and Anne, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Booth Philip (Box 59)
  - Browne, E. V. V., Mrs., correspondence (Box 59)
  - Chinchilla, Carlos Samayoa, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, including Margaret Widdemer, Edna Ferber, and Lynn Fontanne (Box 59)
  - Correspondence regarding studies at Columbia University (Box 59)
  - Correspondence regarding the production of "Mountain Top" (Box 59)
  - Frost, Lesley, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Gillmore, Margalo, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Grant, Jane, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Hastings, Ross, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Invitations, miscellaneous (Box 59)
  - Kelley, Ethel, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Kennedy, Foster, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Kennedy, Foster, miscellaneous papers (Box 59)
  - Kennedy, James, correspondence (Box 59)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, letters to Foster Kennedy (Box 60)
  - Correspondence regarding "Jordan" (Box 60)
  - "The Laurels are Cut", 2 (Box 60)
  - "Lodestar" (Box 60)
  - "Shulo: How the Animals Dug Their Well" (Box 60)
  - Helen Hayes, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Ladd, Valerie, correspondence (Box 60)
  - La, Farge, C. Grant, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Milford, Nancy (Box 60)
  - Millard, Malcolm S., correspondence (Box 60)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Moore, Marianne (Box 60)
  - Parker, Robert Allerton, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Pruitt, Ida, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Shirer, William L., correspondence (Box 60)
  - Skinner, Cornelia Otis, and Mary Kennedy, "Never look back" (Box 60)
  - Tracy, Louise, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Walling, Peggy Wood, correspondence (Box 60)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 3 (Box 61)
  - Correspondence with individuals connected with Shepherd's Nine, 2 (Box 61)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 6 (Box 62)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 4 (Box 63)
  - Date books, 1975, 1986 (Box 64)
  - Lists, miscellaneous (Box 64)
  - "List of lacquer trunk," bound notebook (Box 64)
  - Lists of things to do (Box 64)
  - Notebooks (eleven) (Box 64)
  - Notes, miscellaneous, 4 (Box 64)
  - Notes (Box 64)
  - Notes on dreams (Box 64)
  - Shopper's guide, 1981 April 1 (Box 64)
  - Papers, miscellaneous (Box 65)
  - Obituaries and mass cards for Josephine Kennedy Maner (Box 65)
  - Clippings, miscellaneous, 2 (Box 65)
  - Program, The Barretts of Wimpole Street (Box 65)
  - Maner, Josephine Kennedy, notes (Box 65)
  - Publicity and announcements (Box 66)
  - Cards sent to Mary Kennedy in the hospital and sympathy cards sent to Joan Kennedy after her death, 1987-1988 (Box 66)
  - Moore, Beth, correspondence (Box 66)
  - Poetry manuscripts by others (Box 66)
  - Postcards, blank (Box 66)
  - Sotheby Park Bernet Inc., re: plans to sue (Box 66)
  - Correspondence with Jacksonville friends (Box 67)
  - Correspondence with Savannah relatives and friends (Box 67)
  - Incidental music to "One Day of Spring," by Samuel Barber; autograph manuscript score, 1935 (Box 68)
  - Photographs of Mary Kennedy and colleagues, by Genthe, Steichen, Rabinovitch, and others, 3 (Box 68)
  - Religious memorial photograph ("Most holy father..." for Josephine Kennedy Maner) (Box 68)
  - Portrait photograph of Annie Russell by Albert Petersen, inscribed to Mary Kennedy, 1935 (Box 69 (Oversize))
  - Poster advertising Mary Kennedy in "Dulcy", circa 1930 (Box 69 (Oversize))
  - "Jordan," photostat from 1933 Herald Tribune (Box 69 (Oversize))
  - Barber, Samuel, "One Day of Spring" (music recording, aluminum phonodisc), 1935 (Box 70 (Record Album Storage))
    Conditions Governing Access
    Box 70 contains record album storage. Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.